https://www.rbc.com/privacysecurity/ca/index.html

Privacy and Security
Your privacy is important to us.
Protecting your privacy and safeguarding your personal information is a cornerstone of our organizational ethics and values and will always be one of our highest priorities.
Global Privacy Notice
At RBC, we are dedicated to protecting your privacy and safeguarding the personal information you have entrusted to us.
Our Global Privacy Notice
Accountability and Privacy by Design
What Information We Collect
Why We Use Your Information
How We Use Your Information
Sharing Your Information
Keeping Your Information Safe
Your Right to Access Your Personal Information
Your Choice
Digital Channel Privacy
RBC digital channels offer you control and convenience as well as access to our digital services.
Learn more
Contact Us
Call Us
If you believe your confidential information may have been stolen or obtained by a fraudulent party either online, by telephone or through any other means, call us immediately.
If you believe your confidential information may have been stolen or obtained by a fraudulent party either online, by telephone or through any other means, call us immediately.
Learn more
Report ID Fraud
If you think you are a victim of identity fraud and you are an RBC client
If you think you are a victim of identity fraud and you are an RBC client
Learn more
Email/Website Fraud
If you have received a suspicious email or accessed a fraudulent RBC website
If you have received a suspicious email or accessed a fraudulent RBC website
We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. Any changes will be posted on our website.
